<resources>
    <string name="app_name">BSY NONI</string>
    <string name="product_one_info"><p>Hair colouring process gives birth to problems like allergy, brittle hair, rashes on the scalp and face, irritable skin, asthma and even cancer in the long run. Since, scalp is a skin the chemical get absorbed to the intestinal fluid and blood stream. Due to the continued use of commercial hair dyes people have developed upper respiratory allergies from the pollen, mold and chemicals contained in the product. There have also been severe allergic reactions reported from various parts of the world that even took the life of some and these reactions stem from the dozen chemicals used in the dye. Chemical hair dye is also the cause for the cancer of the lymph tissue. In the later stages this can affect the immune system of the body which in due course will reduce the body ability to fight infections and illness.</p></string>
    <string name="product_one_info_1">The Indian hair color market is worth ? 2,900 crores and has witnessed a growth of 15- 20% every year in the last decade. One of the largest segments is powder hair color or hair dye which due to its ease of use consists of 45- 50% of the market and is growing at 15%. Creme forms 35% due to its higher price point, but growing faster at 20% while Beauty salons are growing almost at the rate of 30-40% in the last few years. With a penetration level of 36%, the market offers huge opportunities for growth. Interest in hair care products remained strong in India during 2015, sales more than doubled from ? 82 billion in 2010 to ?176 billion in 2015. Demand for hair care products is expected to remain strong over the forecast period, with the area having a projected constant 2015 price value CAGR of 8% and sales set to reach ? 262 billion by 2020.\n

        \n• Increasing disposable income.\n
        • Growth in fashion conscious.\n
        • Increase in awareness.\n
        • Increase in male grooming.\n

        \nTherefore, experts advise that it would be safe to use natural hair dyes like black hair magic fruit shampoo which have no harmful reactions.\n

        \n• Usage of herbal products Tie -up with salons.\n
        • 3D colour service.\n
        • Brands seek to be natural.\n
        • Popularity of Do-It-Yourself colorant.\n
        • Usage of harmful chemicals resulting in many lifestyle to life endangering diseases.\n
        • Even people are slowly getting aware of these critical side effects with the help of informative digital era nowadays.\n</string>
    <string name="product_one_usage">• Drink a glass of warm water or filtered water.\n
    \n• Take three drops of Noni or more under the tongue.(Take the drops before brushing your teeth)\n
    \n• Leave it for 1-2 minutes. (This is to allow the juice to be absorbed by the blood vessels under the tongue into the bloodstream)\n
    \n• Consume Noni bit by bit.\n
    \n• Drink another glass of water.\n
    \n• Repeat the process before going to bed.\n
    \n Do not eat or drink any food items containing caffeine (coffee or tea) for the next two hours. Also do not take any other drugs from the clinic or hospital and smoke for the next two hours. (If you are on any medication continue as usual)</string>
    <string name="product_two_info">BSY Group is also launching another product, the pure Noni Enzyme or leaven, a health supplement to restore the health and beauty of the body and mind. The Noni Enzyme is the pure extract of genuine Hawaiian fruit Noni or Morinda Citrifolia.\n\n Noni Enzyme promotes micro circulation and corrects the metabolism processes in the body. The four miracle functions of Noni Enzyme are that it acts as a powerful immune booster, repairs damaged cells, identifies abnormal cells and retards its proliferation and eliminates toxins.\n\n Many of the medicinal benefits though, are largely attributed to the fact that the Noni plant is a source of phytonutrients - which have anti-inflammatory, anti-viral, and antibacterial compounds, known to boost the immune system as well as repair cellular damage.Many of the medicinal benefits though, are largely attributed to the fact that the Noni plant is a source of phytonutrients - which have anti-inflammatory, anti-viral, and antibacterial compounds, known to boost the immune system as well as repair cellular damage.Traditional healers in the Pacific Islands have been using Noni for centuries, as a general wellness tonic - to cure almost any ailment. Today, Noni Enzyme is also considered to be a treatment for cancer and HIV.</string>
    <string name="product_two_usage">\n1) Wet your hair and wipe with a towel.\n
    \n2) Wear gloves and pour the BSY NONI shampoo into a bowl completely and mix well.\n
    \n3) Apply BSY NONI shampoo on hairs and massage vigorously for 5-7 minutes.\n
    \n4) Wash hair with water after 5-10 minutes for desired blackening.</string>
    <string name="product_two_advantage">Healthy Black Within 10 Minutes \nBSY Noni is very easy to apply and takes only ten minutes to set and gives you beautiful, nourished black hair upon washing. It is very easy to use and you can find step by step instructions along with a tutorial video on our website, which will help make the process all the more effortless.\n \nDoubles Up As Hair Conditioner \nHerbal essences such as Noni, Polygonum multiflorum Thunb and Wild Ginseng, Wild Ganoderma Lucidum give the hair a well conditioned look with a healthy shine. It nourishes the hair from the root to the tip and keeps it thick and strong. As a result, it also encourages rapid hair growth.\n \nNutrifies Hair Roots \nWith no chemicals to damage the hair roots and remove the proteins in the hair, and with the copious amount of natural essences present in BSY Noni Black Hair Magic, the hair roots are supplied with nutrients that revitalize the hair, keeping it thick and healthy.\n \nCleanses and Eliminates Dandruff \nThe herbal essences also gives BSY Noni Black Hair Magic anti-dandruff properties by nourishing the scalp and making it healthy enough with regular use to prevent formation of dandruff.\n \nLong Lasting Natural Black Hair \nBeing made of natural components, BSY Noni Black Hair Magic makes your hair look even more black than chemical hair dyes because of the herbs blackening effect. This also ensures that the colour does not fade for a long time.</string>
    <string name="product_two_ingredients">Major Ingredients of this natural colorant includes Noni extract, Wild Ginseng, Polygonum Multiforum and Ganoderma. These are known for their natural dying and medicinal properties worldwide.\n \n• Noni Fruit is a health boon which works on cellular level to restore the health and beauty of body and mind. Noni Fruit is a good source of Vitamins, Calcium, Sodium, Iron and Other Minerals with more than 150+ Nutraceuticals. Anthraquinone naturally found in Noni Plant is responsible for dying properties.\n \n• Ginseng: It contains UV filters to protect the hair from harmful ultraviolet rays of the sun and excessive heat from the hairdryer, Pro Vitamin B5 To restore the health of damaged hair and makes them strong, Vitamin E that stimulates cell regeneration and nourishes the scalp tissue and Allantoin speeds up the natural recovery of damaged cells and stimulates the growth of new hair.\n \n• Polygonum Multiflorum nourishes and blackens hair. It also helps to prevent premature aging of hair.\n \n• Ganoderma Lucidum can fight hair fall and can turn hair back to its natural color. It also works to reduce body toxins.</string>
    <string name="product_two_faq">1) How long does it take for the hair to change colour?\n\nIt takes around 10 minutes for hair to turn black. Make sure the shampoo is applied thoroughly to get the shiny, black hair.\n\n\n 2) How long does the black hair last or fades?\n\n Unlike other hair dye, the black color would not fade. You only need to re-apply the shampoo when there is new growth of white hair.\n\n\n3) Is it possible for the hair to grow naturally black after using BSY Shampoo?\n\nYes, it is possible. After frequent use (once every 4-7 days), eventually the new hair will grow black naturally. It may take a few months to achieve the result. (It will be more effective if used together with Enzymes Noni).\n\n\n4) Is BSY Shampoo a type of hair dye?\n\nNo. This product is not a hair dye. It does not just turn grey hair to black, it also has nutritional value to strengthen hair.\n\n\n5) Does this product leave a stain on headscarves, hats, etc?\n\nNo. Just make sure you wash your hair thoroughly and let your hair dry completely.\n\n\n6) I have a serious hair fall problem. How do I use this product?\n\nMake sure you apply this shampoo thoroughly and massage your scalp. Leave it on your hair a bit longer (about 20 minutes) before you wash your hair. Try adding Noni Enzyme in between shampooing for better result.\n\n\n7) Is it safe for children to use this product?\n\nYes. Children with dandruff problems, scaly scalp and other hair problems are recommended to use this product.\n\n\n8) Is this suitable for everyone?\n\nYes. If you have any doubts, apply a small amount of product on your neck and leave it for 10 minutes. If you does not develop any symptom of allergies, you can use the product.</string>
    <string name="product_one_faq">1) We would like to be appointed as stockists/distributor of BSY Noni in Delhi NCR. Kindly let me know of the formalities and the investment involved.\n\nYou will have to complete the registration formalities to be appointed as stockist/ distributor for BSY Noni. Kindly visit our resources section to get the Dealer Registration Form and details.\n\n\n2) Currently I am Distributor of a Cosmetic product MLM company. I am interested in becoming the super stockist of BSY Noni products in and around Jammu. I would like to get the address where I should apply.\n\nYou can apply online with BSY Noni. But you have to ensure us a strong distribution channel network with you first.\n\n\n3) We are distributors of various food and health supplements. We would like to apply for the distribution of your products in Noida area.\n\nYou have to ensure us a dedicated team and personal attention of BSY Noni Products primarily. As we are getting online orders from whole of the country, we need to ensure a 100% devoted team in case of physical distribution of product. We know that we are going to get a overwhelming response, so you shall be prepared to handled that.\n\n\n4) We run an online shopping portal and are interested in putting up your product range in our website. Let us know who your distributor in Delhi is.\n\nYou can view our Stockist List for specific products on the Product Category pages. In case you still have difficulty in locating a Distributor or Stockist, write to us and our marketing division will get back to you.</string>

    <string name="bpo_bold">BECOME A BSY NONI STOCKIST/DISTRIBUTOR AND ENJOY THE BUSINESS OPPORTUNITIES THAT OUR INCOMPARABLE RANGE OF PRODUCTS AND UNCHALLENGED BRAND DELIVERS. JOIN US TO BUILD A BRIGHT AND HEALTHY FUTURE</string>
    <string name="bpo">BSY Group is an international platform of natural products. We value our customers and their reviews. As per the reviews received by the company from various parts and from our regular customers, we are planning to expand the purview of our product BSY Noni Black Hair Magic followed by Noni enzyme through a network of distributors and channel partners who can satisfy the increased demand from our customers. We have a unique franchise system and business model.</string>
    <string name="bpo_bulltes">• Marketing Support\n • Support From Experts\n • Advertisement Assistance\n • Helps To Accelerate Growth\n • Improve Your Market Knowledge\n • Tools To Develop Your Capabilities\n • Listed As A Distributor On Our Website\n • A Welcome With Full Product Training Knowledge\n • Maximum And Instant Returns In Lowest Investment\n • Unique Products\n • Standardized Products\n • Continuous Ongoing Support\n • Low Investment And High Returns\n • Looking At Market Trend, There Is Surety Of Success\n • Bsy Noni Is Backed By International Companies In Us, China, Etc.</string>

</resources>
